http://www.knitters.org/privacy-policy

Log in
Forgot your password?
HomeGet InvolvedService KnittingVolunteerJoin or RenewWho Are We?Cable Gram BlogCalendarKnitting GroupsLeadershipFree ResourcesOrganizationsYarnYarn Shop DirectoryContact Us
Privacy Policy
Effective January 1, 2010
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Minnesota Knitters’ Guild website. On some pages, you can sign up for membership, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
etc.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete your request or to distribute our newsletter, the Cable Gram, and other relevant information about the Minnesota Knitters’ Guild. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to distribute member information. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, we may tell our Web developer that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
We will make every effort to accurately collect your information. However, you can see all of your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to www.knitters.org and accessing the Members' Area>My Account.
There, you can correct errors in your personally identifiable information yourself.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use the form on the contact us page or send us an email at infomaster@knitters.org.
Join the Guild today!
Get the most out of your love of knitting! Membership benefits include pre-registration for Yarnover, organized public service projects and camaraderie with fellow knitters. Annual dues are $30.
Join
Contact UsSitemapPrivacy PolicyPhoto Disclaimer
Ravelry
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Search ...
Search
© 2010-2020 Minnesota Knitters' Guild, All rights reserved.
Site Developed by Ryvon Designs
